I
welcome you all to my meeting. I
am your friend Abhishek Sharma and today we are going to talk
about the problem stock Asian Paints Limited. Let's talk about
Friday. The
stock's close of Rs 2970 would have given us a straight line and
it would have shown a decline of about 1%.
In this topic, let's see how much a
good deliverable quantity has been
raised in this stock on Friday. That is,
about 140.
This Asian Paints will raise an excellent deliverable quantity of 6% on Friday.
So you must be aware that the
results of these quarters have also been announced. Let
us quickly discuss
their quarter two results.
Easy friends, if we
talk to you about their quarter two results, then on a
year-on-year basis,
we are seeing a decline of 228% in net profit. This
is much less than the expectations within Asian Paints. We will see a decline in net profit. If we
talk about revenue, then
we saw a decline of about 100% in revenue.  A
shine of 32.6 percent is seen in the revenue,
friends, the company says that the
reason for the decline in net profit is the raw
material cost and its increasing
expenses, so due to these
we are seeing a decline in net profit,
friends, let's discuss
their chart view, then the
telecast we have put in front of you, Asian Paints
stock is continuously seeing a decline, if we
talk about the disease, the stock was
made by NAC Shan itself at ₹3509 10,
after that if we look at it here, then it is also visible here, if we talk about the report for the stock, then a
strong support of ₹10 2009 is
seen forming downwards and if this
support is broken, then the stock is
seen turning towards 28, friends, let's
talk about the strategy here that what
strategy should we adopt in the stock in future,
friends, if your photos are
great, definitely include it
here, then you should definitely hold this stock right now, it can
also be seen that
from here you will see the cup pattern  You
can get it but if this stock continues to
fall downwards then soon
this stock is going to break its level of 28, that is the
strategy you have to make, right now there is a great
stock in Asian Paints, so I
made a video to tell this, if you like my videos then
please like, share
and subscribe, thank you very much for watching the video.